[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of the boy on whom Violet has a crush in the film The Incredibles?", "correct_answer": "Tony", "incorrect_answers": ["Craig", "Rodney", "Roger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lady Jane Grey was the uncrowned Queen of England for what period of time in 1553?", "correct_answer": "Nine days", "incorrect_answers": ["Fifteen days", "One day", "One month"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aardvarks have more olfactory nerves than other mammals.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What singer won the 1958 Grammy Award for Best Male Vocal Performance?", "correct_answer": "Perry Como for the song Catch a Falling Star", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Darin for the song Dream Lover", "Domenico Mondugno for the song Nel Blu Dipinto", "Dick Dale for the song Lets Go Tripping"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state motto of Rhode Island?", "correct_answer": "Hope", "incorrect_answers": ["Forward", "The Union", "Industry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to an urban legend, an electrical worker is blinded for life when the following item/s fuse(s) to his eyes.", "correct_answer": "His contact lenses", "incorrect_answers": ["His welding rod", "His goggles", "His loose shirt cuff"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Whoopi Goldbergs character in the 1991 movie Soapdish?", "correct_answer": "Rose Schwartz", "incorrect_answers": ["Celeste Talbert", "Lori Craven", "Montana Moorehead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the world of airplane technology, what does LOT stand  for?", "correct_answer": "Low Observational Technology", "incorrect_answers": ["Long Operational Technology", "Lengthy Oppositional Technology", "Light Opposing Technology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the main colors of turtle-doves?", "correct_answer": "Brown and gray", "incorrect_answers": ["Dark orange and gray", "Pale yellow and some black", "blue and red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What star of Everybody Loves Raymond played Jocko Dundee in Johnny Dangerously?", "correct_answer": "Peter Boyle", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Brad Garret", "Ray Romano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Vadas uncle in My Girl, who had a steel plate put in his head?", "correct_answer": "Phil", "incorrect_answers": ["Dave", "Archie", "Les"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in 1982, 1994 or 2006, what would your lunar sign be?", "correct_answer": "dog", "incorrect_answers": ["rabbit", "snake", "ram"]}]